So our next exercise is very similar to what we just did, the plank.
We're going to add on to that and it's going to be the around the world pushups.
So you're going to come onto your hands and knees just like you did before.
Wide, wide hands.
Same rules apply.
Extend those legs out so you're in your push up position.
So from here, it's going to start with that rock.
You're going to rock towards the right side.
Stay on that right side.
You're going to push down.
Bring your nose towards the mat.
Press up on the left side and all the way up.
So you're making a big circle so you can get all into those shoulders and get those cuts.
Again, left side.
Come over.
Press down.
Bring your nose to the center.
Press and lift all the way up.
Good again.
So you're going to go around the world on the right side.
Hinge over.
Good.
Bend down.
Bring your nose through the center.
Press up on the left side and back in.
Again.
Now you're going to reverse it.
Bring to the left.
Press down all the way.
Bring that nose to that mat.
Press.
Exhale to lift.
So you brought this important here.
Use your breath.
One more right.
Down through center.
Press and lift and again.
And left.
Down through center and down.
So if you're not as strong as Mark is here, you can bend your knees down and do girl pushups and do it the same exact way.
So keep those hips forward.
Again, bend over towards the right side.
Come down through center.
Press up for left and lift.
Still keeping the navel scooped in.
Keeping the shoulders pressed away from the ears and press all the way up.
Press back to child's pose.
Give yourself a good stretch.
Heels towards the butt.
Our next clip will be arabesque pulls.